sup everyone cameras on the t45 he was a
very special video today now I'm back at
you to do a review and of these ass
box now if you're stupid you're probably
wondering why why I'm eating yellow and
blue eyes fast
well that's cuz you're
because people who are smile know
that I chose yellow and blue because
yellow yellow Bobby says yellow and
sapphire blue and Bobby x Sonic is the
good so so yeah you could see this
is like a about ionic about Donna clock
review as pop of you and she now I don't
know like the company who made these but
but it doesn't really matter because
well it's you know you know it's
ice cream baby they all make the same
I'm gonna try the yellow one first
you know we'll see the best of all I saw
all of course try the blue one first
because that's Sonic
boom
I like that I like that like a 10 out of
10 or some next next I'm gonna try
I'll be like like like banana yellow
like Bobby's banana and like
Bobby's yo like a banana
I like that not good tool in better than
the first one about traveling together
cuz you know like Barbie x Sonic I mean
it's just thinking about them having bus
sex sounds good so I won't so I assume I
must taste even better alright that's
good
[Music]
I love that
boom
[Music]
mom's heart modern sock in the
ass mmm I need more how long I wanna do
huh yeah go like Bobby's house yeah
mm-hmm I love it boom
I love it
Tommy under Graham Tommy on the ground
they made our bow the mother will be a
fam sorry got a ground oh I'm not
done with you yeah oh no that blueberry
yeah but I don't know that's a little
Bob know them all right you pick me up
while I'm pulling down beard hmm oh yeah
mm-hmm
this is like a banana